<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tasin Ishmam</title>
    <link>https://tasinishmam.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tasin Ishmam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tasinishmam.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Foobar Challenge</title>
      <link>https://tasinishmam.com/posts/google-foobar-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tasinishmam.com/posts/google-foobar-challenge/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve recently finished Google&amp;rsquo;s coding challenge, Foobar. This has honestly been a really fun programming game, and I wanted to share my experience!
What is it? Foobar is a invite only coding challenge hosted by google. The prize for completing? A chance to be recruited by google. Once you pass a certain level, you have the option to submit your solutions and personal info to a google recruiter. Getting an interview isn&amp;rsquo;t guaranteed however and not everyone gets a response from the recruiters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Lessons From Releasing Our First Public Website</title>
      <link>https://tasinishmam.com/posts/five-lessons-from-first-public-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 16:00:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tasinishmam.com/posts/five-lessons-from-first-public-website/</guid>
      <description>Last month we launched our website coronainbangladesh. In the span of a month, we&amp;rsquo;ve received over 50,000 visitors, news coverage and an acknowledgement in the official Bangladesh Government website. However, having such a high amount of traffic comes with it&amp;rsquo;s own set of challenges. I&amp;rsquo;ve had previous experience developing production systems, but those were mainly Bots, Business integrations and CMS sites which don&amp;rsquo;t receive a fraction of the traffic this had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launch of coronainbangladesh.com</title>
      <link>https://tasinishmam.com/posts/coronainbangladesh-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 21:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tasinishmam.com/posts/coronainbangladesh-launch/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m happy to announce the launch of our website, coronainbangladesh.com.
The objective behind this website was to increase awareness and present reliable infomration about the novel Coronavirus (COVID-19) outbreak in Bangladesh. Everything you need to know about the coronavirus outbreak, in one place.
The novel coronavirus (2019-nCoV) outbreak has rapidly turned into a pandemic. Ever since breaking out in Wuhan, the capital city of Hubei province, China, it has spread to many countries of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reliable Information Sources on Coronavirus</title>
      <link>https://tasinishmam.com/posts/coronavirus-resouces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 15:40:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tasinishmam.com/posts/coronavirus-resouces/</guid>
      <description>There is a torrent of misinformation on the internet about the disease itself, the extent of the infection and government actions taken. As a community if we are not responsible in the information we share, we risk doing more harm than good. In order to get accurate information, we need to use reliable sources and fact-check all information.
With that in mind, this is a curated list of information sources to get one up to date on the COVID-19 situation, both locally and globally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Contact</title>
      <link>https://tasinishmam.com/posts/first-contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 10:46:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tasinishmam.com/posts/first-contact/</guid>
      <description>print(&amp;#34;Hello Internet&amp;#34;) Welcome to my humble corner of the internet. This blog is about me and my passions. I&amp;rsquo;l talk about technology, software development, machine learning, academia and other topics I find interesting.
So, it only makes sense to start by saying how this site came to life. I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about starting a blog for a while now. When I was a child I was a prolific poster in a lot of online communities, forums and review sites.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>